[
  {
    "id": "q0001",
    "question": "feel for",
    "answer": "search by touch"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0002",
    "question": "pluck up courage",
    "answer": "common & idiomatic expression describing the act of summoning courage and strength to do sth difficult or frightening."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0003",
    "question": "take a back seat",
    "answer": "to allow others to take the lead or be in control"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0004",
    "question": "take the bull by the horns",
    "answer": "to confront a difficult situation directly and with determination"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0005",
    "question": "take the plunge",
    "answer": "to make a decision to do something risky or uncertain"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0006",
    "question": "came face to face with danger",
    "answer": "to confront or encounter sth threatening directly"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0007",
    "question": "decided on the spur of the moment",
    "answer": "to make a quick decision without much thought or planning; she decided on her brother's favourite"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0008",
    "question": "show someone the ropes",
    "answer": "to teach someone how to do a job or task"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0009",
    "question": "as fast as his legs could carry him",
    "answer": "to run as quickly as possible. emphasize urgency and maximum effort"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0010",
    "question": "took to his heels",
    "answer": "to run away quickly esp facing danger or trouble"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0011",
    "question": "take the law into one's own hands",
    "answer": "to take action to enforce the law"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0012",
    "question": "take the wind out of one's sails",
    "answer": "to surprise or deflate someone by doing or saying something unexpected"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0013",
    "question": "bring to a boil",
    "answer": "to heat a liquid until it reaches the boiling point"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0014",
    "question": "bring to a head",
    "answer": "to cause a situation to reach a critical point"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0015",
    "question": "defy all odds",
    "answer": "to succeed despite facing significant challenges or obstacles"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0016",
    "question": "stifle a yawn",
    "answer": "to suppress or hold back a yawn"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0017",
    "question": "cut out",
    "answer": "to remove or eliminate; removal by cutting; Ceasing or stopping an action or process"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0018",
    "question": "cut out for",
    "answer": "to be suited or qualified for a particular task or role"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0019",
    "question": "throw a tantrum",
    "answer": "to have an angry outburst or display of frustration,typically by a child"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0020",
    "question": "throw a spanner in the works",
    "answer": "to cause a problem or complication that disrupts a plan or process"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0021",
    "question": "ahead of the curve",
    "answer": "to be more advanced or innovative than others"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0022",
    "question": "face the facts",
    "answer": "accept a hard truth or reality even if it is unpleasant"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0023",
    "question": "washed up on the shore",
    "answer": "fixed expression: carried by wave onto land when a thing is dead or weak"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0024",
    "question": "put on a brave front",
    "answer": "to pretend to be brave or confident in a difficult situation"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0025",
    "question": "put one's foot down",
    "answer": "to assert oneself firmly or insist on a particular course"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0026",
    "question": "distinguish A from B",
    "answer": "to tell the difference between A and B; vs seperate: physically move apart; doesn't tell the difference"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0027",
    "question": "look out for",
    "answer": "to be vigilant or watchful for something"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0028",
    "question": "hold one's weight",
    "answer": "contribute one's fair share to a task or effort. not relying on others to pick up the slack"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0029",
    "question": "hit the roof",
    "answer": "to become extremely angry or enraged"
  },
  {
    "id": "q0030",
    "question": "send for repairs",
    "answer": "general phrase used for fixing damage."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0031",
    "question": "easily accessible by public transport",
    "answer": "convenient to reach using public transportation."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0032",
    "question": "the situation is in hands",
    "answer": "in hand means under control or being managed effectively."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0033",
    "question": "the situation is in good hands",
    "answer": "means that it is being managed by someone capable or trustworthy."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0034",
    "question": "the situation is in flux",
    "answer": "means that it is uncertain or constantly changing."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0035",
    "question": "excuse ready at hand",
    "answer": "at hand means readily available or prepared in advanced."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0036",
    "question": "go on a raid",
    "answer": "fixed expression: to conduct a sudden attack or incursion into a place; \"ON\" is used when talking about organized actions or activities."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0037",
    "question": "decide for oneself",
    "answer": "idiom; emphasize decision is made independently or without external influence."
  },
  {
    "id": "q0038",
    "question": "decide by oneself",
    "answer": "\"by oneself\" emphasizes alone without help."
  }
]